like say welcome brothers and sisters to
another Wednesday question and answer
will we open up with the Ten
Commandments that God had written for
the whole world to keep brother
tanzel and God spake all these words
saying I am the Lord thy God which have
brought thee out of the land of Egypt
out of the house of bondage thou shall
have no other gods before me thou sh I
make to thee any Graven image or any
likeness of anything that is in heaven
the or that is in the earth beneath or
that is in the water under the Earth
thou shall not bow down thyself to them
nor serve them why the Lord thy God I'm
a jealous God visiting the iniquities of
the fathers upon the children until the
third and fourth generation of them that
hate me and showing Mercy unto thousands
of them that love me and keep my
Commandments thou shall not take the
name of the Lord thy God in vain for the
Lord will not hold him Guiltless that
taketh his name in vain remember the
Sabbath day to keep it holy six days
shall thy labor and do all thy work but
the seventh day is the Sabbath of the
Lord thy God and it thou shall not do
any work thou nor thy son nor thy
daughter thy man servant nor thy maid
servant nor thy cattle nor thy stranger
that is within thy gates for in six days
the Lord made Heaven and Earth the sea
and all that in them is and rested the
seventh day wherefore the Lord blessed
the Sabbath day and hollowed it under
thy father and thy mother that thy days
may be long upon the land which the Lord
thy God giveth thee thou shall not kill
thou sh not commit adultery thou shall
not steal thou not bear false witness
against thy neighbor thou not cover thy
neighbor's house thou not cover thy
neighbor's wife nor his man servant nor
his made servant nor his Ox nor his ass
nor anything that is thy neighbors we
read Exodus 21 through 17 and may the
Lord have a blessing to the reading of
his words in Jesus name we pray amen
amen so we on question and answer you
can ask us a question and we'll answer
it according to the King James Bible if
we cannot find the answer we will seek
further counsel to bring you an answer
at a later time keep in mind that all
vague questions will not be answered and
all long scripture questions will not be
answered for time sake but we may be
able to point you in the direction of a
DVD or CD that you can purchase by
calling the office so please be his
director possible with your questions so
we can be as direct as possible with our
answers out of the King James Bible no
other Bibles will be acknowledged on
this program also keep in mind that this
is a live stream and you may begin to
send in your questions at this time even
questions that pertain to everlasting
life we're just asking that you keep
your questions to a two scripture
maximum but let me introduce you to
family that's taking part in the panel
this evening brother Dre good evening
brother Julius good evening everybody
brother Jerome gra and peace Brother
tanzel good evening sister Deborah good
evening brother Sean good evening and we
have the guest caller with us and I'm
brother Cornell sister Deborah what is
our first question of the
evening uh yes there are uh there are
several held over questions that will be
answered first before getting into
tonight's
Q&A so uh a
AHS what does it mean when God says he
will recompense to Edom and obah 1 vers
15 and
16 and Amos 9 vers 11 and 12 are given
all right share some light on those two
vers versus brother Julius let's go to
that uh ob one brother tenzel ob one uh
recom the word the definition of
recompense is to pay back for something
done or
suffered to pay back for something done
or or suffered almost like we going the
Lord going to reward you for your
behavior when you get
it let's read this scripture pel let's
read this
scripture and pick it up at
verse
15 for the day of the Lord is near upon
all the Heathen as thou Hast done it
shall be done unto thee thy reward shall
returned upon thy own head and there you
go there's your answer right there for
violence against your brother for what
did you do back up and read verse 10 go
ahead for thy violence against thy
brother Jacob shame shall cover thee and
thou sht be cut off forever verse
13 thou should us not have enter into
the gates of my people in the day of
their Calamity yeah thou shouldest not
have looked on their Affliction in the
day of their Calamity nor have laid
hands on their substance in the day of
their Calamity continue neither should
us thou have stood in the Crossway to
cut off those of his that did Escape
neither should as thou have delivered of
those of his that did remain in the day
of his distress so now because of uh
edom's uh Behavior toward his brother
Jacob and the hatred that he had toward
his brother the Lord said uh because you
have done this to my people it's going
to be done to you now read verse 15
again and that'll be it for the day of
the Lord is near upon all the heathens
as thou has done it shall be done unto
thee and thy reward shall return upon
thy own head so the definition of
recompense is to pay back for something
done or something suffered just like the
Lord say because Israel has suffered
greatly the Lord is going to uhh reward
them for their suffering it is going to
be a good reward and then you can go to
Amos ninth chapter it's the same exact
those scriptures mirror each other you
know so we'll forego that one because
it's the same thing it's dealing with
the same subject matter you want to hit
that you want to hit that verse 16 and
that obadi that they asked about too
yeah verse 16 continue to read it for as
he have drunk upon my Holy Mountain so
shall all the heathens drink continually
yeah they shall drink and they shall
swallow down and they shall be as they
have not been because of what they did
in
Jerusalem uh what they did in Jerusalem
the Lord's going to pay you back for
what you did in Jerusalem and all the
nations that come up against Jerusalem
is going to be paid back for what they
did against the children of Israel
that's all I
got all right thank you for that brother
and like you said that Amos will mirror
what you just uh shed some light on yes
amamos the night ter Mir is the same
thing all right thank you for for that
sister Deborah our next question next
question Miss Wade asked in James 1 vers
26 and 27 the word religion how should I
understand this word pertaining to
Salvation all right brother Dre um how
do you um use that word pertaining to
Salvation use the word pertaining to
Salvation
by doing what the faithful do let's go
to James one and pick it up at verse
22 and then we'll read down into it go
ahead but e doers of the word and not
hearers only deceiving yourselves yeah
because if you just a hearer of the word
you deceiving yourself and your religion
is vain now skip down to verse 25 go
ahead but whoo lookth into the perfect
law of Liberty and continu with therein
he being not forgetful hearer but doer
of the work this man shall be blessed in
this deed so if you a doer of the work
you will be blessed in your deed and
that is how it pertains to Salvation 26
and 27 go ahead but if any man among you
seem to be religious and brith not his
tongue but deceiveth his own heart
this man's religion is in vain so
bridling your tongue means don't say
everything that you think in your head
don't let everything that you thinking
come out of your mouth you should have
something that governs your tongue and
it should be the word of God go ahead
pure religion and undefiled before God
and the father is this to visit the
fatherless and widows in their
Affliction and to keep himself unspotted
from the world and you keep yourself
unspotted from the World by being a doer
of the word of God not just the hero
only right hope that
helps all right thank you for that
brother as we continue to move on to our
next question next question Solomon yby
Jr asks what is what is the urum and
thum
Jerome what is the Y and
Thum uh they're put in the breastplate
of the high priest from among the uh
sons of Aaron it's it's the breastplate
that they wear and that's where it's
located okay let's go take a look at it
go to Exodus
28 and read verse
29 and 30
get it go ahead and read
it and Aaron shall bear the names of the
children of Israel in the breastplate of
judgment upon his heart when he goth in
when he go in unto the holy place for a
memorial before the Lord
continually and thou shall put in the
breastplate of Judgment of urum and the
the thumm and they shall be upon Aaron's
heart and when he goth in before the
Lord and Aaron shall bear the Judgment
of the children of Israel upon his heart
before the Lord continually yeah so
that's where they located they located
on the breastplate of the uh high priest
of the sons and
air that's all I got
on all right hope that ansed your
question as we continue to move on to
our next question moving on Valencia
asked for you to explain Matthew 19
verse3 Matthew 19 verse3 let's go to
that Matthew
19:30 go ahead and read it and the guest
caller we share some light from
here but many that are first shall be
last and the last shall be
first okay what he's telling you is
let's let's just go and read let's go to
Matthew the 21st
chapter and we're going to read from we
going to start reading at verse uh
28 and uh
um down to uh to
43 go ahead when you get there but what
think ye a certain man had two sons and
he came to the first and said Son go
work today in my
Vineyard and he answered and said I will
not but afterward he repented and went
and he came to the second and said
likewise he answered and said I go sir
and went not whether of them Twain did
the did the will of his father and they
said unto right here he had the Lord say
this man had two sons he told one to go
and work in the field he said okay but
he didn't go then he told the other son
go and work in the field he said no I'm
not G but then he repented and he went
now the question was which one obeyed
keep
reading so whether them Twain did the
will of his father and they said unto
him the first Jesus said unto them but
verily I say unto you that the publicans
and the Harless go into the kingdom of
God before
you for John
came now now he said now
look one that says he he wasn't and he
went so he's talking to religious people
here he said Mama tell un say unto you
that the public in the harage go into
the kingdom before you cuz you got these
people running around saying they serve
God and they in church all the time but
they don't keep no Commandments and you
get the street people you know the you
know the hustlers and hollers and people
out there that have never heard the word
when they hear it they believe and they
repent but the people in think they have
it they don't repent go ahead and read
but John came unto you in the way of
righteousness and ye believed him not
but the publicans and the Harless
believed him and ye when ye have seen it
repented not afterward that ye might
believe
him so now so he said look John the
Baptist
came and y'all didn't believe him but
the public in the hollers it's the
street people leader so now who going to
go into the
kingdom the bans and the Harland so the
people that call themselves serving God
and all in church all the time and up
front they are the
first but then the public and the holl
that didn't claim to believe nobody
until they got the real truth and they
turn to God then they are the
last so they going to go in before the
first in fact the first ain't going to
go in at all read the rest of
it here another Parable there was a
certain householder which planted
a that's enough we don't have to go no
further okay first the first are the
people that claim to serve
God and the land of the people that
don't claim to serve
God but when they hear like the Publican
the H the people that don't claim to
serve God when they heard John the
Baptist out there preaching they heard
him and they repented
but the so-called religious people out
there the uh Pharisees and and the ones
that sit in Moses seat they didn't
believe John the Baptist so they didn't
repent but they were the
first but they ain't going to get into
the
kingdom but the people that believe the
publicans in the holl of the street
people and and repent they are going to
get into the kingdom therefore the uh uh
uh last is go go in before the first
that's all I have to
say all right hope that answers your
question as we move on to our next next
one Kaz says my mother and I got
into uh a semi heeded disagreement about
the Book of Enoch and she was saying the
Lord took Enoch Elijah and Mary to
heaven and I told her no I need a Bible
verse telling her
no all right um guess call in regards to
these people going to heaven can you
share some
light okay let's go and see what Jesus
said let's go into St John the 3 chapter
and read verse
13 yes sir and no man have ascended up
to heaven but he that came down from
heaven even the son of man which is in
heaven who is the son of man isin that
Jesus that's right
but he said no man has ascended to
Heaven that's gone to heaven except for
he that came down uh uh Enoch was a man
wasn't it that's right yeah was a man
right and Mary even though she female
she's still a
man now let's go into First Timothy the
6th chapter read 13
through6 First Timothy 6 tanzel
13 through
16 and I give thee charge in the sight
of God who Quicken all things and before
Christ Jesus who before pontian pilot
witness a good
confession that thou keepest this
commandment without spot unrebuked until
the appearing of our Lord Jesus
Christ which in his times he shall show
who is the bless and only ponent the
king of kings and Lord of lords who only
have immortality dwelling in the light
which no man can approach unto who no
man have seen nor can see to whom be
honor the power Everlasting
amen do not you tell your testimony of
Jesus who only have
immortality dwelling in the light that
no man can see have seen or will seen
what light is that that's the light of
third heaven a't nobody on
there now
Enoch uh uh didn't die but he didn't go
there because Enoch was a man before he
was
changed and that light remember God said
let there be light and later on uh on
this he he created light again with the
sun and the moon to put light on the
earth that light that no man has seen
will see can see and will see is that
light that he created in the thir Heaven
that's where the father dwell now for
the rest of them that you know that died
like Elijah and Moses and
Mary let's see when they going to get
theirs let's go into First Corinthians
the 15th chapter read verse 21-
23 but since by Man Came Death by man
came also the resurrection of the Dead
for as in Adam all died even so in
Christ shall all be made alive but every
man in his own order Christ the
first look as an all die in Christ
everybody shall be made alive right
that's right if you was in heaven
wouldn't you be
alive but he said but but read but he
said but every man in his own order
start back at there but every man in his
own order Christ the first fruits
afterwards they that are Christ and his
coming so Christ is not here is he no
sir so now those that are Christ they
will be made alive at his coming being
that he haven't came yet everybody
that's ever died is still dead and Enoch
that didn't die he did not go to heaven
because Jesus is the only
one that dwell in that light where no
man can approach approach
uh and have approach and will
approach that's all I have to say all
right thank you for that hope that
answer their question as we continue to
move on to our next question next
question Malik Shure asked in Revelation
8 verse1 why was there a silence in
heaven about the space of an half an
hour all right Revelation 8 and and one
Let's uh let's go there this is just a
time before them trumpets start blowing
and terrible trumpets begin to blow but
let's go and read that Revelation
8 and pick it up at that verse one they
want to know about space of a half an
hour all right Revelation 8 And1 yes sir
and when he had opened the seven seal
there was silence in heaven about the
face of a half an
hour all
right open to
the what was the question why was there
yeah what does um the space of about a
half an hour
mean no no what did the question say the
question
said why was there a silence in heaven
about the space of in half an hour
that's why I thought the question was
and the answer to that is we don't know
that's
right all right we'll leave it right
there and move on to our next question
moving on cash in
888 notes says if shaving your head was
wrong wouldn't job have failed the test
but the Lord said say
not brother Dre what you say
well let's go read about what was said
with job let's go to uh job the first
chapter and pick it up at Verse 18 Job 1
and8 and we gonna read the
22 okay go ahead 1 18 while he was yet
speaking there came also another and
said thy son and thy daughter were
eating and drinking wine in their eldest
brother's
house and behold there came a great wind
from the Wilderness and smoked the four
corners of the house and it fell upon
the young men they are dead and I only
am escaped alone to tell thee so job
lost his children here and what did job
do go
ahead then job arose and rent his manle
and shaved his head and fell down upon
the ground in
worship go ahead and said naked came I
out my mother's womb and naked shall I
return thither
the lord gave the Lord have taken away
blessed be the name of the
Lord go ahead and in all this job sin it
not nor charg God foolishly so job did
not sin by doing this but let's go to um
let's go to
um what is the scripture I'm looking for
here let's go to
Genesis no
uh uh Leviticus
21 Leviticus
21 and pick it up at verse one Leviticus
21 and one go ahead brother Leviticus 21
And1 the Lord said unto Moses speak unto
the priest the sons of Aaron and say
unto them there shall none be defiled
for the dead among his people MH but for
his kin that is there unto him that is
for his mother and for his father
for his son and for his daughter and for
his brother
uhhuh so this is talking to the priest
the sons of Aaron right and he said you
shouldn't be defiled except for near of
Ken mother father son daughter or his
brother go
ahead and for his sister that is not
unto him which which hath had no husband
for her may he be defiled
go ahead he shall not defile himself
being a chief man among his people to
profane himself uhhuh they shall not
make baldness upon their head neither
shall they shave off the corners of
their beard nor make any cuting in their
flesh okay so we see here this is what
this is talking about for the dead and
then you have exceptions here and this
is talking about the sons of Aaron but
we just read in Jo that job did not sin
when he did that so I I I'm sure you
read it as well but for your answer sake
yes job did not sin by doing
that that's it right thank you for that
brother hope that answered their
question as we move on sister deil with
a Time Check Yes the time is
7:58 uh a Thomas asked
what was in Jesus Cup in Matthew
26:39 all right let's go to Matthew
26 and his cup was coming to die for the
sins of the world that's why he was sent
and in that cup was pain
Affliction death and
Resurrection but let's go to that
Matthew
26 and let's pick it up brother
at verse
26 go
ahead Matthew 26 and 26
yes and as they were eating Jesus Took
bread and blessed it and break it and
gave it to the disciples and said take
eat this is my
body and he took the cup and gave thanks
and gave it to them saying drink ye all
of it but this is my blood of the new
testament which is Shar for many for the
remissions of sins so that was what was
in his cup too that he had to shed his
own blood for the remission of sins all
right skip down to verse 36 and go
ahead then cometh Jesus with them unto a
place called
gatam and said unto the disciples sit ye
here while I go and pray
Yonder and he took with him Peter and
the two sons of zebede and began to be
sorrowful and very
heavy then say he unto them my soul is
exceeding sorrowful even unto death so
Terry ye here and watch with
me and he went a little further and fell
on his face and pray saying oh my father
if it be possible that this cup pass
from me nevertheless not as I will but
as thou will and the alsoo in that cup
was him being exceeding sorrowful
because if flesh had kicked in and they
were coming to do a real hate killing on
him skip down and read 41 and
42 watch and pray that ye enter not into
temptation the spirit indeed is willing
but the flesh is weak and he went away
again the second time and prayed saying
oh my father if this cup may not pass
away from me except I drink it thy will
be done so he came to drink of the cup
that him and the father had agreed upon
that he would die for the sins of the
whole world and so let's go to First
Corinthians 5 and read one verse 1
Corinthians
5 First Corinthians
5 because he was having also the
Passover with his disciples there when
he took the bread and the wine and let's
see who died for us go
ahead um what verse seven Purge out
therefore the old Le that ye may be a
new love as ye are unle for even Christ
Our Passover is sacrifice for us so that
was in that cup too that he had to do
came and he was sacrificed for us died
for the sins of the whole world so that
we may have access back to that tree of
eternal life that's right that's all I
got
I like we hope that that answer oh guest
caller go right
ahead I'mma go physical on you instead
of spiritual all right so now read that
again what he said about what he said
when he had in the cup
Matthews Matthews 26 verse
39 and he went a little further and fell
on his face and prayed saying oh my
father
no I'm talking about the original
question that is the original question
what was in Jesus Cup in Matthew 26
verse
39 okay read
it and he went a little further and fell
on his face and prayed saying oh my
father if it be possible that this cup
pass from me nevertheless not as I will
but as thou
will okay
I'm going go physical the physical is
that if I you know that uh uh if it's
possible for me to keep from
dying for the sins of the people then
let me but not my will but thy will okay
in short he didn't want to
die okay that's all I wanted to add all
right hope that answered your question
as we move on to our next next one Leia
said I was trying to explain to my
mother that when we pass we go straight
to the ground where we came from then
she argues about where do the soul go
when we
pass all right brother Julius share some
light the the problem is you're arguing
with your mother instead of both instead
of maybe you know but you instead of
arguing with her sit down give her a
Bible and you have your Bible and you
read and you read let's go and this is
what you read to her let's go to Genesis
and7 Genesis chapter 2 and and read
verse 7 and let's really pay attention
to this read it slow stanzel because I
want you to you're going to use this to
highlight we're going to highlight some
things in here Genesis 2:7
that's right Genesis 2 and7 yes sir and
the Lord God formed man of the Dust of
the ground St right there man is dust
man came from dust so you highlight man
and you highlight dust he came from dust
now the Lord formed man from the dust of
the ground what else did God put in the
man to make him live go ahead and
breathe into his nostril the Breath of
Life and Man became a living Soul so now
to mobilize this man he had to put
breath in him you can't see it because
it's spiritual so the spirit of life is
the Breath of Life in this context okay
so now and it says Man became a living
soul that is the sum total of you you
are a living Soul while you alive you're
live you're living Soul when you're poor
you're a poor soul when you're happy
you're a happy soul and when you die you
are a dead Soul let's let me show you
this right here Genesis chap
3el man sinned against God broke the
Commandments and now the wages of sin is
death so now what happens to a person
when they die and what is the last thing
that lead the body let's go and read
verse 19 go ahead in the sweat of thy
face shall thou eat bread till thou
return unto the ground so now
highlight the word or underline the word
return you came from the ground and you
come from you go back to the ground when
you die but the breath don't go back
into the ground because it is spiritual
God put the body where it came from and
the breath belongs to him
continue for out of it was thou taken
for dust thou are and into dust shall
thou return and that's why when you die
you have a funeral they take you to the
cemetery and that's that is for a place
for dead folks now a soul you can read
Leviticus chapter 5 a soul is a body we
just read that theand is a soul a soul
is a body you can read that in Leviticus
uh the 5th chapter but forsake of time
let's go to Ezekiel the 18th
chapter and I got one scripture after
this Cornel Ezekiel the 18th
chapter because Man became a living Soul
so the difference between spirit and
souls is Spirit don't die you can't kill
it you can punish it forever or you can
reward with everlasting life but you
cannot kill
Spirit Ezekiel 18 read verse 4 and then
read verse 20 what happens to souls go
ahead 18 eel 18 and4 18 and4 behold All
Souls are mine as The Souls of the
father so also the soul of the son son
is mine the soul that sinth it shall die
how do we know that because Genesis the
3r chapter verse 19 said thust you are
and unto thust shall you return so Souls
die verse 20 the soul that sinth it
shall die he told you again the soul
that sinth it shall die last place job
the 34th
chapter let's pay attention to this job
chap 34 and verse 14 so sisters or
brothers in start of arguing read the
book read the book that way you take out
any
guest 34 and 14 remember where he got
man from the dust of the ground 34 and
14 we gonna read 14 and 15 tzel let's
go if he set his heart upon man if he
gather unto himself his spirit and his
breath notice the spirit and the breath
is interchangeable in this context so
now man if he set us off hard upon man
if he take back him to himself his
breath which is spiritual what happens
All Flesh Shall Perish together and man
shall return again unto dust and man
shall turn again to death uh unto dust
that's why the book that's why you every
funeral they say ashes the ashes which
is mean the cream to body and dust to
dust you came from dust and you go back
to dust but the Lord takes back the
breath that is why when the person dies
or animal dies anything that's living
dies it goes back to the
dust and because it don't have no breath
in it it dies and go back to the dust
and the Lord takes back to breath
because everything that's living is
breathing I hope that helped Cornel
can I can I add a little bit to that
just just to what he
said Ecclesia uh 12 and 7 ecclesiastic
12 and verse 7 then shall the dust
return to Earth as it was and the spirit
shall return unto God who gave it and
that is the breath that goes back that's
why when you see people on the operating
table and they they they they dying or
they're trying to resuscitate them they
trying to make them breathe again
right yep all
right just call it go
ahead First Corinthians 15th chapter
verse
45 First Corinthians
15 and verse
45 1 Corinthians 15 and 45 thank you gu
caller and so it is written the first
man Adam was made a living Soul the last
Adam and that's s said the first man
Adam was made a living soul
and that cos signs what Moses wrote in
in Genesis 2 and 7 don't it yes sir and
Man became a living Soul you are the
soul when you die the soul die
that's a lot of scripture that should
help go ahead I'm through all right we
gonna leave it right there sister
Deborah our next question next question
Zion asked in Ecclesiastes 7 verse 17
does that mean you can die before your
time or does that verse mean something
else all right brother Jerome what you
say yeah that mean exactly what it say
let's go read
it Ecclesiastes 7 verse1
17 ecclesiastic
7-17 be not over much Wicked neither be
thou foolish why should thou die before
thy
time he said be not over much Wicked
neither be thou foolish why should you
die before your time he let you know you
can die before your time okay one other
verse and then that'll be it go to
Proverbs chap 10 verse
27 proverbs 10 yeah verse 27 and verse
27 the fear of the Lord prolong of days
but the years of the wicked shall be
shortened yeah the years of the wicked
shall be short so yeah that's all I got
him yes sir
need to be trying to get that righteous
together brother Jerome amen all right
hope that ansed your question as we move
on to our next next one living humbly
says I had a disagreement with someone
the other day because I said God
divorced Israel but not Judah was I
right that he never divorced
Judah yes Cara what you say
okay yeah he was right never did first
let's look let's go to
Isaiah the uh uh 50th
chapter and read verse one show you that
Israel will divorc 50 and one Isaiah 50
and one thus sayith the Lord where's the
bill of your mother's divorcement whom I
have put away or which of my creditors
is it to whom I have sold you behold for
your iniquities have you sold yourselves
and for your transgression is your
mother put
away now let's go and find out who he's
talking
to let's go into Jeremiah the 30
chapter and we're going to read 6
through 11 and let's see who was theor
here who was mentioned
here 6 through
11 J 3
6-1 the Lord said also unto me in the
days of Josiah the king hast thou seen
this which backsliding Israel have done
she has gone up upon every high mountain
and under every Green Tree and there
haveth played the
Harlot that I have said after she have
done all these things turn thou unto me
but she returneth not and her teach and
her treacherous sister Jud saw it and I
saw with
all that mention both of them don't it
Israel did all kind of sin and say her
treacherous sister Judah saw okay so
let's see who you're going to divorce
keep reading and I saw when all the
causes whereby backsliding Israel
committed adultery I have put her away
and given her a Bild of a divorce yet he
tres
he said black tra back slideing Israel
didn't it I put her away and I gave her
a bill of divorcement go
ahead and yet her treacherous sister
Judah feared it not but went and played
the Harlot
also what verse are you that was in
eight HEB read and it came to pass
through the likeness of her whoredom
that she defiled the land and committed
adultery with stones and with
stocks and yet for all this her
treacherous sister Judah have not turned
unto me with her whole heart but fely
said the Lord and the Lord said unto me
the backsliding Israel have Justified
herself more than treacherous
Judah so go and Proclaim these words
toward the North and say return thou
backslide in Israel sayeth the Lord and
I will cause my anger to fall upon you I
am merciful say the Lord and I will not
keep anger
forever what verse is that that's end of
12 so the whole thing out of all that
who did he uh uh uh give bill of
divorcement according to what's written
Israel Israel that's the northern
kingdom but said Judah did so much that
he and and Judah did so much sin that uh
he made Israel uh Justified but the Lord
did not divorce Judah the Lord divorced
Israel the northern kingdom 10
tribes so you're
right he did not divorce Judah only
Israel that's all happened all
right all right thank you for that hope
that answered that question as we move
on to our next next one Stephen googus
asked in Micah 7 verse5 what does this
scripture mean is the woman of thy bosom
a man's wife are they are there any
precepts to this
scripture all right T let's go to Micah
7 and verse
5 Guess caller take it from
there Michael 7 ver verse
five trust ye not in a friend and put ye
not confidence in a GU keep the doors of
thy mouth from her and life in thy
bosom now that is talking about his wife
let's go to Malachi the 2 chapter read
13 through
15 give scripture
again that's Malachi 2
13-15 Malachi 2
13-15 and this have ye done again
covering the altar of the Lord with
tears with weeping and with crying out
in so much that he regardeth not the
offering anymore or receive it with Good
Will at your hand but yet ye say
wherefore because the Lord have seen
witness between thee and the wife of thy
youth against whom thou has dealt
treacherously yet is she thy companion
the wife of thy Covenant and did not he
make one yet had he the residue of the
spirit and where and wherefore one that
he might seek a Godly seed therefore
take heed to your spirit and let none
deal treacherously against the wife this
youth
now a wife of his bosom the wife of his
Youth and the wife of his his
Covenant it's talking about the same
thing the wife that you have there
nothing else outside of that who the
wife of your bosom she is the wife of
your Covenant because you had to marry
her you ENT into a
covenant and if you m her young then she
is the wife of your youth however way
you look at it he is merely talking
about a man's wife that's all I have to
say yes all right hope that answered
your question is we move on to our next
question next question he also uh
says sometimes I want to pray while I'm
driving but not always facing
Jerusalem will the Lord still hear my
prayer even though I'm not facing
Jerusalem yes indeed Lord can still hear
your prayer no matter what direction you
facing north south west Jerusalem
happens to be in East but we stand on
class on the Sabbath day and face the
East because the Lord say his eyes will
always be there and so will his heart
perpetually so we we all do it in
Oneness it's a beautiful thing to see
but yeah the Lord can hear you and when
you're in your car while you driving and
you want to pray hey your brother make
sure you take off your hat and pray your
sister should make sure your head is
covered when you do pray let's go to
Matthew Matthew 12 right quick Matthew
12 we get that Matthew 12 brother just
read uh
35 through 37 because he was asking well
God hear his prayer even though he's not
facing
Jerusalem go ahead a good man out of
good Treasure of the heart bringeth
forth good things and evil man out of
the evil treasure bringeth forth evil
things uhhuh but I say unto you that
Every Idle word that men shall speak
they shall give account thereof in the
day of judgment y for by Thy word thou
shall be justified and by Thy word thou
shalt be condemned so yeah Lord can hear
your prayer no matter which way you may
be facing so doesn't always have to be
toward
Jerusalem but that's what we call HED in
the bet if you so are able to do that
it's a good idea that's all I
got and we hope that that answers your
question as we move on to our next
question next question his last question
is in Isaiah 60 verse 8 and9 is this
referring to some people traveling by
plane and boat to the Wilderness in the
time of
trouble all all right brother Julius
what you say now yes it is and you can
read psalms uh uh
91 about that you know that the
Wilderness is a place of protection it's
also a place of purging but you going to
get there by whatever modes of
transportation that are available ships
by planes um there's another scripture
that I'm looking for I can't call it
right away um where it say you gonna be
flying on Eagle wings another way and
that is by the power of God but you
those are literal airplanes and and
ships uh like when you see the ships of
tares um that's how you travel by by
boat and mainly by boat and by plane
whatever destination the Lord bring us
from Into the Wilderness yes that's all
I
got was that Revelation 12 and 14
maybe the question uh came from is
Isaiah 68 and9 right let's uh let's read
it let's read
it I'm sorry Isaiah 60 and verse
89 who are these that fly as a cloud and
as the doves to their Windows yes surely
the ow shall wait for me and the ships
of tares first to bring thy sons from
far and their silver and their gold with
them unto the name of the Lord thy God
and to the the Holy One of Israel
because he ha glorified
thee
yes y so that's what that mean that's
how you gonna get there by ships and by
by uh ships and by
ples all right what was that you
had I don't know if that was the uh the
verse that Julius was looking for it
said uh great eagles wings or something
like that yeah it was in uh Revelation
12 and 14 that have those uh words in it
so that you gonna flee Into the
Wilderness
[Music]
yeah all
right okay we'll leave it there and um
we keep moving right on along sister
Deborah as we go into new territory
correct yep yes we are now into
tonight's Q&A for Wednesday November the
2024 time out Houston says if God's law
forbids Human Sacrifice why did he
accept Jesus as a human
sacrifice God's law forbids Human
Sacrifice which it does sacrificing kids
in the fire and all that stuff that
those other nations used to do but why
did he accept Jesus as a human sacrif
ACF because Jesus came to die for the
sins of the whole world that's right so
let's go into um 1 Timothy 3 first
Timothy
3 and let's see who it is we talking
about here because actually even to put
Jesus as a human
sacrifice beside um this man
sacrificing Jesus too big for that
sentence let's go to First Timothy 3 and
read verse 16 when you get there
brother and without conf the one that
did the the sacrifice for us go
ahead and without controversy great is
the mystery of
godliness God was manifested in the
flesh justified in the spirit sing of
angels preached unto the Gentiles
believed on in the world received up
into Glory this is the one that came and
died for the sins of the whole world God
got off his throne and came and put on
this filthy flesh and came and died for
the sins of the whole world now who sent
him in John 3 janzel let's go there
quickly John
3 when you get there pick it up at
that at verse 15 for me
St John
3:15 go ahead that whosoever belied in
him should not perish but have eternal
life yeah for God so loved the world
that he gave his only begotten son that
whosoever believeth in him shall not
perish but have everlasting life that's
why he accepted this sacrifice of Jesus
we thank God El all of us will be cut
off go ahead brother but God said not is
son into the world to condemn the world
that the world through him might be
saved yes skip down to verse 34 for
me for he whom God have S speak the
words of God for God giveth not the
Spirit by measure unto him uhhuh the
Father loveth the Son and have given all
things into his
hand and he that believeth on the son
have everlasting life and he that
believeth not the son shall not see life
but the wrath of God abideth on him so
he was accepted as a human sacrifice
because the father sent him and he came
and died for the sins of the whole world
and now he's sitting back at the right
hand of the father and he is pleading
our
Cs and that's all I got on that Cornel
can we read that 1 Corinthians 15 and
one verse verse
21 1 Corinthians 15 and 21 and
21 all right well says by Man Came Death
by man came also the resurrection of the
dead yes so he had to die so that we
might
live and that sacrifice was Jesus that's
right good add on thank you thank you
for that brother as we move on to our
next question moving on uh Israel for
life asked in Genesis is one it says
Birds came from the
water and it is given he gave or she
gave Genesis 1 verse 20 but in and it
continues on but in Genesis 2 verse 19
it says they were formed from the ground
how should we understand this
difference all right brother Dre let's
go all the way back to the beginning and
share some light brother yes sir let's
go to Genesis 1 we going to read verse
20 and then we'll go read Genesis 2 and
19 go ahead tanzel when you get it and
God said let the waters bring forth
abundantly the moving creatures that
have light and fouls that may fly above
the Earth in the open firmament of
Heaven now let's go to Genesis 2 and
read verse
19 and out of the out of the ground the
Lord God form every Beast of the field
every foul of the air and brought them
unto Adam to see what he would call them
and whatsoever Adam called every living
creature that was the name thereof so we
see here he said out of the ground right
now let's go back to Genesis one and we
gonna start at verse one read verses one
and two go ahead and the beginning God
created heaven and the Earth the Earth
was without form and void and dark was
upon the face of the deep and the spirit
of God moved upon the face of the waters
you say the Earth was without form and
void and darkness was upon the face of
the deep and the spirit of God moved
upon the face of the waters skip down
verse n Go
ahead and God said let the waters under
the heaven be gathered together un one
place and let the dry land appear and it
was so well now wait a minute the dry
land didn't appear because it was under
the waters until God said let the dry
land appear and it was so go
ahead and God called the dry land Earth
and the Gathering Together of the waters
called he sees and God saw that it was
good so God and God said let the Earth
bring forth the grass and Herb yielding
seed and so on and so forth now let's go
to second Peter the third chapter second
Peter 3 and we going to read verses 5
and
six go ahead when you get it
brother but this they wly are ignorant
are ignorant of that by the word of God
the heaven were ofok and the Earth
standing out of the water and in the
water whereby the world that then was
being overflowed with water perished so
he talking about the world that then was
it was overflowed with water and it
perished so the Earth was under the
water but when you reading about those
files they came forth from the earth
when he said let the dry land appear and
he created those things he's letting you
know all that was under the waters and
it came forth so I hope that
helps all right thank you for that
brother as we move on to our next
question okay uh this person also asked
in Genesis 1 it
says in Genesis
1 God seemed to have a clear plan
creating everything in order but in
Genesis 2
it uh it feels like he's figuring things
out especially when creating a woman for
a man what's the why why the
difference yes
carer why don't we go to Genesis the
first chapter and read we're going to
start from verse 24- 28 then we're going
to skip down to verse
31 Genesis 1
and uhuh 24-
28 and God said let the Earth bring
forth the living creatures after his
kind cattle and creeping things and
beasts of the earth after his kind and
it was so and God made the Beast of the
earth after his kind and cattle after
their kind and everything that creepeth
upon the Earth after his kind and God
saw that it was
good and God said let us make man in our
image after our life Ness let them have
dominion over the fish of the sea and
over the fowls of the air and over the
cattle and over all the Earth and over
every creeping thing that creepeth upon
the Earth so God created man in his own
image in the image of God created he him
male and female created he
them and God blessed them God said unto
them be fruitful and multiply and
replenish the Earth subdue it and have
dominion over the fish of the sea and
over the foul of the air and of every
living thing that moveth upon the Earth
and read verse
31 and God saw everything that he had
made and behold it was very good in the
evening and the morning were the sixth
day so he made he made all the Beast of
the field and all you know man and all
that he here the first chapter tell you
what he did and the second chapter tell
you in the order that he did it 2
and8 Genesis
2:18 the Lord God said it is not good
that man should be alone but I will make
him a help meat for
him and out of the ground the Lord God
formed every beast of the field every
fowl of the air and brought them unto
Adam to see what he would call them and
whatsoever Adam called every living
creature that was
thereof and Adam gave name to all
cattles and to the fowls of the air and
to every beast of the feeld but for Adam
there was not found a help meat for him
and the Lord God caused a deep sleep to
fall upon Adam and he slept and he took
one of his ribs and closed up the flesh
instead thereof and the rib which the
Lord God have taken from man made he a
woman and brought her unto the man man
and Adam said this is now bone of my
bones and Flesh of My Flesh she shall be
called woman because she was taken out
of man therefore shall man
leave that's that's enough now verse
chapter God telling you what he
did and the second chapter he is telling
you how and in the order that he did it
ain't no confusion
there first first one God tell you what
he did second one he tell you how he did
it and the order that he did it that's
why it said man that that that uh man
should not be
alone then he brought it in
order also in the second chap first
chapter he told told you that God
created Man Out of the Dust of the
ground I mean that God created man male
and female on the second chapter it
tells you how he did it
so the first chapter the Lord telling
you what he did and the second chapter
he's telling you how he did it and in
the order that he did it there's no
confusion there that's all I have to
say all right I'm going to move on to
our next question sister Deb with the
time check yes the time is uh
8:36 um so he answer uh the guest caller
answered the fourth question that uh he
had uh had about Genesis again about the
the animals are created before man and
woman but in Genesis man is created
first and the animals and then finally
the woman so he was wanted to know why
is there a difference in the order of
creation is there an answer to that why
creation
there is no difference in the order of
creation the first chapter is just
telling you what what all he
did but the second chapter set it in
order that's why it said God say it's
not good that man should be alone that
let you know that there was nobody
before him then after that he brought up
the animal then later on because he
trying to he said I'm going to create a
help that's good for him that's meat for
him now so first he brought forth that
animal that wasn't enough so then he
went put Adam to sleep and brought forth
the will and created woman so it was
know so the first chapter was telling
you all he created he just happened to
name the Beast before Adam but to set
everything in order that second chapter
said it is not good that man should be
alone that let you know now you going to
get some order
here like the first chapter is like a
blueprint no it's not a
blueprint okay first chter is telling
you what he
did
okay all right we'll leave it right
there as we continue to move on sister
Deb yes moving on Randy Sims asks can
you celebrate New Year's is coming up in
December yes carer can you celebrate
that New Year's is coming up next month
the
31st you can if you want to but there
not God's New Year so if it's not God's
New Year there is not a new
year that's all I have to
say God's New Year starts in
Mar what are you celebrating you're
celebrating a lie
all I have to all right my next question
sister next question Andrew says could
you explain Exodus
23:13 is there any cultural context or
should I refrain from saying Pagan God's
names if I can and then he throws in uh
also my friend has recently decided to
convert to Christ I am in Australia so I
cannot take him to church what else can
I do to help
him brother Julius I'm G answer that
second question first you could tell him
to go to I OG and tune in to all of the
Israel God's
lessons until we get something uh uh
established in uh physically Australia
that's the answer to the second question
now let's go to Exodus uh the 23rd
chapter and read verse 13 10 because um
you got to name God because the Bible
names Gods what you cannot do is bow
down to them and worship them so let's
read that 20 uh 23 and 13 Exodus 23
and13 and in all things that I have said
unto you be circumspect and make no
mention of the name of other gods
neither let it be heard out of that
mouth so this is what you have to do in
all things that I have said circumspect
be the definition of circumspect is to
be careful and you have to carefully
consider the uh careful when you're
being careful in consideration of the
circumstances the circumstances you have
to understand the circumstances of what
you're doing and what you're
saying you have to be careful with that
and I'm going give you an example of
that so you're
circumspect uh in all things that I have
said unto you be circumspect and make no
mention un circumspect you have to be
careful of the consequences of what
you're saying and what you're doing and
make no mention of the name of other
gods neither let it be heard out of thy
mouth let's get the answer to this right
here Exodus the 20th chapter
this why you have to be careful with the
god of
Israel Exodus 20 and when you get it
read verse one and then jump down to
verse three go ahead T and God spake all
these words saying thou shall have no
other gods before me so respect God you
don't have no other gods before me so
now you have to be careful of the
consequences of doing this continue
thou shall not make in the any Graven
image or any likeness of anything that
is in heaven above or that is in the
earth beneath or th is in the water
under the Earth go ahead thou shall not
bow down thyself to them nor serve them
why here the consequence here's the
consequence now go ahead why the Lord
thy God am a jealous God visiting the
iniquities of the fathers upon the
children unto the third and fourth
generation of them that hate and that's
why you have to be careful of the Ten
Commandments and and and and violating
them because there are consequences
behind it and the Lord say he is a
jealous God and he gonna pay you a visit
that's right so that's what that
scripture mean I hope that
helped all right we gonna move on to our
next question it's time is just a
running yes can nothing wrong with
mentioning other gods because you have
to you have to mention him to correct
people just like the book says about
Deon and about Malcolm and about kees
all these pagan gods and look what
happened to them pagan gods and look
what happened to the people that worship
them that's why you have to be
circumspect you got to be careful that's
all I got I'm sorry yeah and old Deon
got beat up too didn't he Julius got
broken up and end up worshiping uh the
Arc of the Covenant working worshiping
the god of Israel that is correct
all right hope that answered your
question next
question next question Tama says I
understand that the dead know nothing
according to the scripture but will the
dead that are raised at the coming of
Christ be informed about what took place
in the world while they were
sleep all right brother
Jerome well the dead that's going to be
raised uh at the coming of Christ are
those that's going to make the first
resurrection and if they make the first
resurrection they going to be God so
they going to know what God know you
know he going to give them
everything you know they going to
inherit everything including the
knowledge you go they going to know what
God know so let's let's go to
um 1 Corinthians the 13th chapter
and read verse
9-10 1 Corinthians 13 verse 9-10 when
you get it go ahead for we know in part
and we prophesy in
part but when that which is perfect is
come then that which is in part shall be
done away and Jesus who is perfect when
he come
he going this going to be a first
resurrection and those that are in
Christ going to meet them in the air the
dead and those that are alive you know
and they going to become God all right
you promis them they Throne they going
to be judges ain't going to be judge
they gonna be the judge okay one more
verse Revelations
21 and read verse
7 Revelation
21 7 yeah that over cometh shall inherit
all things that will be his God and he
shall be my son yeah he said inherit all
things that include the knowledge that's
all I
got could I add something to that
Cordell yeah go ahead you can know
everything you need to know right now
while you are alive while you are alive
you could you're reading this book you
understand the plan of God you
understand the first resurrection you
understand the great white thr judgment
and you die with that knowledge you die
with that knowledge and even though you
in the grave you got the knowledge
before you died and that's what and you
walk in the Commandments and keep the
commandments so I expect to become God
because the book told me while I'm
living that I will be God if I Endure
until the end so I expect that even
though I'm dead and when I come out to
that grave I will be what I learned when
I was in the flesh and blood body that's
all I
got yeah cuz I know um cuz they want to
know too what they be updated on what
took place while they was taking a nap
but you already know we know about
what's going on right now we know what's
coming we know about the European Union
we know about all these things we know
about the kings of the East so we know
about these
things so it's just that when you raise
up all that stuff is fulfilled and
you're going to do your part uh in the
armor of the Lord because it's already
written yeah
all right we gonna move on to our next
question next question Peter Johnson
asks was Satan kicked out of heaven and
then put in the Garden of
Eden let's open that up to the panel
yeah Satan was definitely kicked out of
heaven no doubt and he was in the Garden
of Eden panel anything
add there ain't nothing else to add the
Bible tell you where he he was in the
garden of e all right that's Genesis
chapter 3 Genesis chapter 3 was there he
is the tree of the knowledge of Good and
Evil well let's go and read that right
quick don't take a lot of
verse so then we can go ahead and put
that to put that the rest
there what verse you said it was
Julia uh Genesis uh chapter chapter 3
and
one all
right now the serpent was more subtile
than any beast of the field which the
Lord God had made and he said unto the
woman yeah have God said you should not
eat of every tree of the
garden and the woman said unto the
serpent we may eat of the fruit of the
Trees of the garden so there you go he's
in the garden there only four beings in
the Garden of Eden the tree of life
which is Jesus the tree of the knowledge
of Good and Evil which is none other
than Satan the devil or The Serpent and
Adam and
Eve in Garden somebody up talks about it
too somebody grab that right
quick thou H has been in Eden the Garden
of God what is that Ezekiel 28 yeah
that's it that's it that's
Ezekiel we in search Mo be coming up
with that shortly
Ezekiel
28 Ezekiel
28 eel
28 and we G start with the king that's
verse 13 you want to get straight to
it yeah yes please all right Ezekiel 28
and
uh 13
13 thou has been in the garden of God
precious stone was thy Covenant the sage
topaz and the diamond the burrow and onx
and the Jasper the sapphire the emerald
and the carbon and gold the workmanship
of thy tabs and of thy pipes were
prepared in thee in the day that thou
was created
yeah go ahead
sorry
ver thou are the anointed cheriff that
cover it and I have set the soul thou
was upon the holy mountain of God thou
has walked up and down in the midst of
the stones of
fire goe and thou was perfect in thy
ways from the day that thou was created
till iniquity was found in thee by the
multitude of thy merchandise they have
filled the midst of thee with violence
thou has sinned therefore I will cast
thee as profane out of the Mountain of
God and I will destroy the old covering
chair from the midst of the Stone of
fire that SS it don't it
yep it was right there in the garden of
e that's right all right hope that
answered your question next question
next question brother Anthony horsey ask
you to share some light on Matthew 11
verse1 what does it mean yet the one who
is least in the kingdom is great
than he John the Baptist and can you
also shine some light on verse 12 how
does the kingdom suffer violence and
taken by
force Matthew
11 Matthew 11 and
11 verely I say unto you among them that
are born of women there have not risen
up greater than John the Baptist not
withstanding he that is least in the
Kingdom of Heaven is greater than he all
right open to the panel guest calling
you want to start that off and why why
because John the Baptist was flesh and
blood and as long as he was living he
could have
sin but if you are in the kingdom of God
then you are
God so no if you was a a like Solomon
said what did he say he would he be a
doorkeeper in the Kingdom still you in
the Kingdom you are an immortal you
can't die no more John the Baptist could
because he was Flesh and Blood the least
in the kingom is greater the least in
the Kingdom that mean that you're a God
you uh uh uh you're greater than the
greatest in in in Flesh and Blood
form because you have accomplished the
purpose that God brought created us me
now what was the rest of
it uh verse 12 and can you share some
light on verse 12 how does the kingdom
suffer violence and taken by
force that's because they killed the
prophets they even killed John the
Baptist y but the Lord Rectify that when
he come back they even kill Jesus
that's a violence okay they tried to
shut it all down Satan did through
man yeah and and it says even until now
it's still a lot of violence going on oh
they kill him look what they did with
the apostles they chased them around I
think Herod killed killed James one of
them and was going to kill Peter but the
angel let him
go that's the that is talking about
Kingdom that's the people that represent
the
kingdom yeah yeah the Lord said you
going to suffer many things for my
name's
sake and they and and and the kingdom is
still suffering from violence that's
right when you turn around tell the
truth then people come against you then
the time going to come during the uh uh
three and a half years of Great
Tribulation people going to be beheaded
for the name of the Lord
yep yep
so the kingdom going to suffer violence
till the Lord come and then he going to
drop some violence on the people that's
creating the
violence all it is to that all right
sister Deborah time
check time is
854 next question in uh sister
Tanisha uh asks in Second Kings 21 verse
6 what does it mean when manessa made
his son pass through the
fire all right Second Kings 21
and6
yes tanzel when you get there don't you
read that and what does it mean when
manasse made his son pass through the
fire sound like a sacrifice of his son
but Glory read it brother and let's open
it up to the
pound and he made his son pass through
the fire and observed times and using
ments and dealt with familiar Spears and
wizards and he brought much wickedness
the in the sight of the Lord to provoke
him to anger yes open to verse
two and he did that which was evil in
the sight of the Lord at the abomination
of the Heathen whom the Lord cast out
before the children of
Israel yeah verse three say he worshiped
and all that stuff so he made his son do
the same thing that he did
[Music]
and a lot too Julius of those um other
nations that the lord gave us they land
they were sacrificing and having their
kids pass through the fire then and the
Lord said don't be like them people and
we turned around and was just like those
people that's why he told you that's why
the Lord said don't I I separated you
from Other Nation don't learn their ways
or they gon take you
yep can we read um Leviticus 18-
21 Leviticus 18 and
[Music]
yeah 18 and 21 Leviticus 18 and
21 and thou shall not let any of thy sea
pass through the fire to mole neither
shall thou profane the name of thy God I
am the Lord so a lot of times doing that
because they was offering to them pagan
gods yeah in other other words they
burning their children in the fire
y yeah yeah that's what it's called
that's
what they making Human
Sacrifice yeah yeah yeah that's that's
plain right there yeah and it did indeed
provoke the Lord to
anger that's
it all right sister Deborah next
question next question Zion asked in
Psalms 5 verse5 does God hate the sins
of a person committing the sin I hear
people say God does not hate it's the
sin that he
hates so Psalms 5
verse5 all right let's pick it up at at
verse four and let's read down into that
five and then let's let's open it up to
the panel because God don't have no
pleasure at all in wickedness he can't
stand it he's longsuffering and patient
go ahead uh brother t for thou art not a
God that have pleasure in wickedness
neither shall evil dwell with thee and
the foolish shall not stand in thy sight
and thou hatest all workers of iniquity
the question again
deah the question again is does God hate
the sin
or the person committing the
sin well both of them yeah both of them
that's right he can hate to he hate to
sin as we just read but when you will
for sin and you continue to do that Lord
don't like you either you know it's
wrong and you just keep doing it so like
Julia said it can be both the sin or the
person is doing the sin the end ver
verse five answers it he says Thou
hatest all workers of
iniquity that's the person in sin who
going into the Lake of
Fire
Sinners the the person that committed
the
sin y so hey learn what righteousness is
and do
it all right our next question all right
brother Jay ass in Deuteronomy 28:
49-52 what nation is this and where they
come from and when it happened so
Deuteronomy 28 vers 49- 52 what nation
is this and and where they come
from and when it happened let's go there
and read that tanzel this is our last
question of the evening Deuteronomy 28
start at 49 brother go ahead the Lord
shall bring Nation against thee from far
from the ends of the Earth Earth as
Swift as the eagle fly a nation whose
tongue thou shall not understand a
nation of fierce continents which shall
not regard the perss of the old nor
shall favor to the young and he shall
eat the fruit of thy cattle and the
fruit of thy land until thou be destroy
which also shall not leave thee neither
corn wine or oil or the in increase of
thy kind or flocks of thy sheep until he
have destroyed thee and he shall besiege
thee in all thy Gates until thy high and
fense walls come down wherein thou
trusted throughout all thy land and each
shall bece thee in all thy Gates
throughout all thy land which the Lord
thy God have given thee this is all
because of Disobedience the question
deah was what who is these nations yeah
uh what nation is that say where did
they come from and when and when did it
happen all right guess caller you want
to win who is this nation and when did
it happen like
Babylon yeah that was there was
Nebuchadnezzar and Babylon y
y yeah that's where they come from those
are the ones that scattered see the
Assyrians took out was the nation uh uh
that uh uh took out the 10 tribe but in
this particular case is talking about
Judah
and uh that's Babylon and when was it
done in 606
BC all right okay
so what a good point to end our session
on this evening with a little history
there and sister de we have ran out of
time yes the time is
9:01 we want to thank everybody from all
around the world who tuned in with us
this evening and we say that if you
submitted a question question and we
didn't have a chance to get to it please
don't resubmit sister Deborah take it
put it in rotation and we will deal with
that question next week so we thank you
all again and until we all come together
again be safe be blessed may the Lord
have mercy on us all brother tanzel
close us out Our Father which are in
heaven Hallowed be thy name thy kingdom
come thy will be done in earth as it is
in heaven give us this day our daily
bread and for forgive us of our debts as
we forgive our debtors and lead us not
into temptation but Deliver Us from Evil
for thine is the kingdom and the power
and the glory forever in Jesus name we
pray amen
amen good night all